<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="quote1">We cannot solve problems with the kind of thinking we employed when we came up with them.” — Albert </string>
    <string name="quote2">Learn as if you will live forever, live like you will die tomorrow.” — Mahatma Gandhi</string>
    <string name="quote3">Stay away from those people who try to disparage your ambitions. Small minds will always do that, but great minds will give you a feeling that you can become great too.” — Mark Twain</string>
    <string name="quote4">When you give joy to other people, you get more joy in return. You should give a good thought to happiness that you can give out.”— Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
    <string name="quote5">When you change your thoughts, remember to also change your world.”—Norman Vincent Peale</string>
    <string name="quote6">It is only when we take chances, when our lives improve. The initial and the most difficult risk that we need to take is to become honest. —Walter Anderson</string>
    <string name="quote7">Nature has given us all the pieces required to achieve exceptional wellness and health, but has left it to us to put these pieces together.”—Diane McLaren</string>
    <string name="quote8">Success is not final; failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." — Winston S. Churchill</string>
    <string name="quote9">It is better to fail in originality than to succeed in imitation." — Herman Melville</string>
    <string name="quote10">"The road to success and the road to failure are almost exactly the same." — Colin R. Davis</string>
    <string name="quote11">“Success usually comes to those who are too busy looking for it.” — Henry David Thoreau</string>
    <string name="quote12">“Develop success from failures. Discouragement and failure are two of the surest stepping stones to success.” —Dale Carnegie</string>
    <string name="quote13">"Nothing in the world can take the place of Persistence. Talent will not; nothing is more common than unsuccessful men with talent. Genius will not; unrewarded genius is almost a proverb. Education will not; the world is full of educated derelicts. The slogan \'Press On\' has solved and always will solve the problems of the human race." —Calvin Coolidge</string>
    <string name="quote14">“There are three ways to ultimate success: The first way is to be kind. The second way is to be kind. The third way is to be kind.” —Mister Rogers</string>
    <string name="quote15">“Success is peace of mind, which is a direct result of self-satisfaction in knowing you made the effort to become the best of which you are capable.” —John Wooden</string>
    <string name="quote16">“I never dreamed about success. I worked for it.” —Estée Lauder</string>
    <string name="quote17">“Success is getting what you want, happiness is wanting what you get.” ―W. P. Kinsella</string>
    <string name="quote18">“The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty." — Winston Churchill</string>
    <string name="quote19">“Don\’t let yesterday take up too much of today.” — Will Rogers</string>
    <string name="quote20">“You learn more from failure than from success. Don\’t let it stop you. Failure builds character.” — Unknown</string>
    <string name="quote21">“If you are working on something that you really care about, you don\’t have to be pushed. The vision pulls you.” — Steve Jobs</string>
    <string name="quote22">“Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterwards.” ―Vernon Sanders Law</string>
    <string name="quote23">“To know how much there is to know is the beginning of learning to live.” —Dorothy West</string>
    <string name="quote24">“Goal setting is the secret to a compelling future.” — Tony Robbins</string>
    <string name="quote25">“The two most important days in your life are the day you\’re born and the day you find out why.” – Mark Twain</string>
    <string name="quote26">“Nothing ever goes away until it teaches us what we need to know.” – Pema Chodron</string>
    <string name="quote27">"We can see through others only when we can see through ourselves.” – Bruce Lee</string>
    <string name="quote28">“First forget inspiration. Habit is more dependable. Habit will sustain you whether you\'re inspired or not. Habit will help you finish and polish your stories. Inspiration won\'t. Habit is persistence in practice.” ―Octavia Butler</string>
    <string name="quote29">“The best way out is always through.” ―Robert Frost</string>
    <string name="quote30">“The battles that count aren\'t the ones for gold medals. The struggles within yourself—the invisible, inevitable battles inside all of us—that\'s where it\'s at." —Jesse Owens</string>
    <string name="quote31">“If there is no struggle, there is no progress.” —Frederick Douglass</string>
    <string name="quote32">“Someone will declare, “I am the leader!” and expect everyone to get in line and follow him or her to the gates of heaven or hell. My experience is that it doesn\’t happen that way. Others follow you based on the quality of your actions rather than the magnitude of your declarations.” ―Bill Walsh</string>
    <string name="quote33">“Courage is like a muscle. We strengthen it by use.” —Ruth Gordo</string>
    <string name="quote34">“Relentlessly prune bullshit, don\'t wait to do things that matter, and savor the time you have. That\'s what you do when life is short.” —Paul Graham</string>
    <string name="quote35">"More is lost by indecision than wrong decision.” —Marcus Tullius Cicero</string>
    <string name="quote36">"If the highest aim of a captain were to preserve his ship, he would keep it in port forever." —Thomas Aquinas</string>
    <string name="quote37">"You can be the ripest, juiciest peach in the world, and there's still going to be somebody who hates peaches." —Dita Von Teese</string>
    <string name="quote38">“Keep a little fire burning; however small, however hidden.” ―Cormac McCarthy</string>
    <string name="quote39">“It is remarkable how much long-term advantage people like us have gotten by trying to be consistently not stupid, instead of trying to be very intelligent.” —Charlie Munger</string>
    <string name="quote40">“You can\’t be that kid standing at the top of the waterslide, overthinking it. You have to go down the chute.” —Tina Fey</string>
    <string name="quote41">“When I believe in something, I\’m like a dog with a bone.” —Melissa McCarthy</string>
    <string name="quote42">“And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom.” —Anaïs Nin</string>
    <string name="quote43">“The standard you walk past, is the standard you accept.” —David Hurley</string>
    <string name="quote44">“I\'ve searched all the parks in all the cities and found no statues of committees.” —Gilbert K. Chesterton</string>
    <string name="quote45">“Success is stumbling from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm.” ―Winston Churchill</string>
    <string name="quote46">“Keep your eyes on the stars, and your feet on the ground.” ―Theodore Roosevelt</string>
    <string name="quote47">“Do not stop thinking of life as an adventure. You have no security unless you can live bravely, excitingly, imaginatively; unless you can choose a challenge instead of competence.” ―Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
    <string name="quote48">“Perfection is not attainable. But if we chase perfection we can catch excellence.” —Vince Lombardi</string>
    <string name="quote49">“Get a good idea and stay with it. Dog it, and work at it until it\’s done right.” —Walt Disney</string>
    <string name="quote50">“Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence.” —Helen Keller</string>
    <string name="quote51">“Concentrate all your thoughts upon the work in hand. The sun\'s rays do not burn until brought to a focus. “ — Alexander Graham Bell</string>
    <string name="quote52">“Either you run the day or the day runs you.” — Jim Rohn</string>
    <string name="quote53">“I\’m a greater believer in luck, and I find the harder I work the more I have of it.” — Thomas Jefferson</string>
    <string name="quote54">“When we strive to become better than we are, everything around us becomes better too.” — Paulo Coelho</string>
    <string name="quote55">“Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work.” — Thomas Edison</string>
    <string name="quote56">“Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible.” — Tony Robbins</string>
    <string name="quote57">“Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. And the only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven\'t found it yet, keep looking. Don\'t settle. As with all matters of the heart, you\'ll know when you find it.” — Steve Jobs</string>
    <string name="quote58">“It\’s not about better time management. It\’s about better life management” — Alexandra of The Productivity Zone</string>
    <string name="quote59">“You\'ve got to get up every morning with determination if you\'re going to go to bed with satisfaction.” — George Lorimer</string>
    <string name="quote60">“Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world.” — Nelson Mandela</string>
    <string name="quote61">“The most difficult thing is the decision to act, the rest is merely tenacity.” —Amelia Earhart</string>
    <string name="quote62">“You\’ll find that education is just about the only thing lying around loose in this world, and it\’s about the only thing a fellow can have as much of as he\’s willing to haul away.” —John Graham</string>
    <string name="quote63">“Take the attitude of a student, never be too big to ask questions, never know too much to learn something new.” —Augustine Og Mandino</string>
    <string name="quote64">“The elevator to success is out of order. You\’ll have to use the stairs, one step at a time.” — Joe Girard</string>
    <string name="quote65">“Be a positive energy trampoline – absorb what you need and rebound more back.” — Dave Carolan</string>
    <string name="quote66">“People often say that motivation doesn\’t last. Well, neither does bathing – that\’s why we recommend it daily.” — Zig Ziglar</string>
    <string name="quote67">“Work until your bank account looks like a phone number.” — Unknown</string>
    <string name="quote68">“I am so clever that sometimes I don\’t understand a single word of what I am saying.” — Oscar Wilde</string>
    <string name="quote69">“People say nothing is impossible, but I do nothing every day.” — Winnie the Pooh</string>
    <string name="quote70">“Life is like a sewer… what you get out of it depends on what you put into it.” — Tom Lehrer</string>
    <string name="quote71">“I always wanted to be somebody, but now I realise I should have been more specific.” — Lily Tomlin</string>
    <string name="quote72">“Talent wins games, but teamwork and intelligence win championships.” — Michael Jordan</string>
    <string name="quote73">“Individual commitment to a group effort—that is what makes a team work, a company work, a society work, a civilisation work.” — Vince Lombardi</string>
    <string name="quote74">“Teamwork is the ability to work together toward a common vision. The ability to direct individual accomplishments toward organizational objectives. It is the fuel that allows common people to attain uncommon results.” — Andrew Carnegie</string>
    <string name="quote75">“Coming together is a beginning. Keeping together is progress. Working together is success.” — Henry Ford</string>
    <string name="quote76">“Alone we can do so little, together we can do so much.” — Helen Keller</string>
    <string name="quote77">“Remember, teamwork begins by building trust. And the only way to do that is to overcome our need for invulnerability.” — Patrick Lencioni</string>
    <string name="quote78">“I invite everyone to choose forgiveness rather than division, teamwork over personal ambition.” — Jean-Francois Cope</string>
    <string name="quote79">“Just one small positive thought in the morning can change your whole day.” — Dalai Lama</string>
    <string name="quote80">“Opportunities don\'t happen, you create them.” — Chris Grosser</string>
    <string name="quote81">“Love your family, work super hard, live your passion.” — Gary Vaynerchuk</string>
    <string name="quote82">“It is never too late to be what you might have been.” — George Eliot</string>
    <string name="quote83">“Don\'t let someone else\'s opinion of you become your reality” — Les Brown</string>
    <string name="quote84">“If you\’re not positive energy, you\’re negative energy.” Mark Cuban</string>
    <string name="quote85">“I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.” — Stephen R. Covey</string>
    <string name="quote86">“You can get everything in life you want if you will just help enough other people get what they want.” —Zig Ziglar</string>
    <string name="quote87">“Inspiration does exist, but it must find you working.” —Pablo Picasso</string>
    <string name="quote88">“Don\'t settle for average. Bring your best to the moment. Then, whether it fails or succeeds, at least you know you gave all you had.” —Angela Bassett</string>
    <string name="quote89">“Show up, show up, show up, and after a while the muse shows up, too.” —Isabel Allende</string>
    <string name="quote90">“Don\'t bunt. Aim out of the ballpark. Aim for the company of immortals.” ―David Ogilvy</string>
    <string name="quote91">“I have stood on a mountain of no\’s for one yes.” —Barbara Elaine Smith</string>
    <string name="quote92">“If you believe something needs to exist, if it\'s something you want to use yourself, don\'t let anyone ever stop you from doing it.” —Tobias Lütke</string>
    <string name="quote93">“Don\'t look at your feet to see if you are doing it right. Just dance.” ―Anne Lamott</string>
    <string name="quote94">“Someone\'s sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago.” —Warren Buffet</string>
    <string name="quote95">“True freedom is impossible without a mind made free by discipline.” ―Mortimer J. Adler</string>
    <string name="quote96">“Rivers know this: there is no hurry. We shall get there some day.” ―A.A. Milne</string>
    <string name="quote97">“There is a vitality, a life force, an energy, a quickening that is translated through you into action, and because there is only one of you in all time, this expression is unique. And if you block it, it will never exist through any other medium and will be lost.” ―Martha Graham</string>
    <string name="quote98">“Small is not just a stepping-stone. Small is a great destination itself.” ―Jason Fried</string>
    <string name="quote99">“He that can have patience can have what he will.” ―Benjamin Franklin</string>
    <string name="quote100">“The only one who can tell you “you can\’t win” is you and you don\’t have to listen.” —Jessica Ennis</string>
    <string name="quote101">“Set your goals high, and don\’t stop till you get there.” —Bo Jackson</string>
    <string name="quote102">“Take your victories, whatever they may be, cherish them, use them, but don\’t settle for them.” —Mia Hamm</string>
    <string name="quote103">“Life can be much broader once you discover one simple fact: Everything around you that you call life was made up by people that were no smarter than you. And you can change it, you can influence it… Once you learn that, you\'ll never be the same again.” —Steve Jobs</string>
    <string name="quote104">“Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance you must keep moving.” —Albert Einstein</string>
    <string name="quote105">“What you do speaks so loudly that I cannot hear what you say.” —Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
    <string name="quote106">“I have never let my schooling interfere with my education.” —Mark Twain</string>
    <string name="quote107">“If you can\'t yet do great things, do small things in a great way.” ―Napoleon Hill</string>
    <string name="quote108">“If you really want to do something, you\'ll find a way. If you don\'t, you\'ll find an excuse.” ―Jim Rohn</string>
    <string name="quote109">“Be sure you put your feet in the right place, then stand firm.” ―Abraham Lincoln</string>
    <string name="quote110">“Live out of your imagination, not your history.” —Stephen Covey</string>
    <string name="quote111">“Do not wait for the perfect time and place to enter, for you are already onstage.” —Unknown</string>
    <string name="quote112">“The greater the difficulty, the more the glory in surmounting it.” ―Epicurus</string>
    <string name="quote113">“Courage doesn\'t always roar. Sometimes courage is a quiet voice at the end of the day saying, "I will try again tomorrow."“ —Mary Anne Radmacher</string>
    <string name="quote114">“If the decisions you make about where you invest your blood, sweat, and tears are not consistent with the person you aspire to be, you\’ll never become that person.” ―Clayton M. Christensen</string>
    <string name="quote115">“Fear of what other people will think is the single most paralyzing dynamic in business and in life. The best moment of my life was the day I realized that I no longer give a damn what anybody thinks. That\’s enormously liberating and freeing, and it\’s the only way to live your life and do your business” — Cindy Gallop</string>
    <string name="quote116">“The only way of discovering the limits of the possible is to venture a little way past them into the impossible.” ―Arthur C. Clarke</string>
    <string name="quote117">"Worry is a misuse of imagination." —Unknown</string>
    <string name="quote118">“Courage is the most important of all the virtues because without courage, you can\'t practice any other virtue consistently.” ―Maya Angelou</string>
    <string name="quote119">"I never look back, darling. It distracts from the now." —Edna Mode</string>
    <string name="quote120">"A year from now you will wish you had started today." —Unknown</string>
    <string name="quote121">"The reason we struggle with insecurity is because we compare our behind-the-scenes with everyone else\’s highlight reel." —Steve Furtick</string>
    <string name="quote122">"Somewhere, something incredible is waiting to be known.” —Carl Sagan</string>
    <string name="quote123">“I will not lose, for even in defeat, there\’s a valuable lesson learned, so it evens up for me.” —Jay-Z</string>
    <string name="quote124">“I do not try to dance better than anyone else. I only try to dance better than myself.” —Arianna Huffington</string>
    <string name="quote125">“If you don\’t risk anything, you risk even more.” —Erica Jong</string>
    <string name="quote126">“Failure is simply the opportunity to begin again, this time more intelligently.” — Henry Ford</string>
    <string name="quote127">“Our greatest glory is not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall.” — Confucius</string>
    <string name="quote128">“If you change the way you look at things, the things you look at change.” — Wayne Dyer</string>
    <string name="quote129">“We must reach out our hand in friendship and dignity both to those who would befriend us and those who would be our enemy.” — Arthur Ashe</string>
    <string name="quote130">“It\'s fine to celebrate success but it is more important to heed the lessons of failure.” — Bill Gates</string>

</resources>